Guide to the Louis Walinsky papers, 1978-1992.
Walinsky, Louis papers, 1978-1992
- Daily Records - COPIES, April - June 1956 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Daily Records - COPIES, July - September 1956 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Daily Records - COPIES, October - December 1956 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Daily Records - COPIES, January - March 1957 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Daily Records - COPIES, April - June 1957 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Daily Records - COPIES, July - August 1957 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Daily Records - COPIES, November - December 1957 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Daily Records - COPIES, January - March 1958 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Daily Records - COPIES, April - June 1958 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Daily Records - COPIES, July - September 1958 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Daily Records - COPIES, October - December 1958 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Daily Records - COPIES, January 1959 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Dictabelt Reports - ORIGINALS, April - December 1956 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Dictabelt Reports - COPIES, April - December 1956 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Dictabelt Reports - ORIGINALS, January - December 1957 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Dictabelt Reports - COPIES, January - December 1957 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Dictabelt Reports - ORIGINALS, January - July 1958 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Dictabelt Reports - COPIES, January - July 1958 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Dictabelt Reports - ORIGINALS, August 1958 - January 1959 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Dictabelt Reports - COPIES, August 1958 - January 1959 (Box 12, Folder 30)